吸血鬼后裔  前情提要
Previously on Legacies...
我女儿乔西
My daughter Josie
受了黑魔法的影响
is under the influence of black magic.
你说你回来是有原因的
You said you came back here for a reason.
融合日快乐
好了  撒旦姐姐
All right, Sister Satan,
我们开始吧
let's dance.
手足相系
... generis fiantus.
别哭了  爸爸
Don't cry, Dad.
少了一个要照顾的人
One less mouth to feed.
她觉得她赢了
She thinks she won.
霍普有个备用计划
Hope had a plan B.
霍普在乔茜的意识里吗
Hope's in Josie's mind?
我们用那个黑魔法来召唤并且控制
Let's use that dark magic to raise and control
- 马里沃  - 如果我们召唤他
- Malivore himself. - If we raise him
然后他得到了兰登的能力
and he gets his dirty hands on Landon...
我已经对柯比先生有了安排
I have plans for Mr. Kirby.
这倒是出乎意料
Well, this is unexpected.
乔西
Josie?
你的潜意识让我起鸡皮疙瘩
Your subconscious is weirding me out.
面包屑
Literal bread crumbs.
出自《汉赛尔与格莱特》，收录于《格林童话》
兄妹俩前后经历了两次遗弃第二次被遗弃 汉赛尔用面包屑做记号
却被鸟儿啄食干净 兄妹俩在森林中迷了路
一点都不含蓄
Subtle.
等等  没事的
Wait. It's okay.
你不用跑
You don't have to run.
暗尽光来
Post tenebras spero lucem.
你也不用躲
You don't have to hide, either.
我不会伤害你的
I'm not gonna hurt you.
你能不能把你的嘴闭上  女士
Would you shut your piehole, lady?
在我们被杀掉之前
And put out that light,
把光熄掉
before you get us both killed.
第2季   第16集
吸血鬼后裔
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
查德
Chad!
把长袍拿过来
Get the robes!
我们要举行仪式
We must have ceremony.
凤凰对我们的计划不再是威胁了
With the phoenix vessel no longer a threat to our plans,
今天我们就要召唤马里沃
today's the day we raise Malivore!
翻 译  Lysenko
你
Wha...
你对我的地方做了什么
What have you done to my crypt?
整理了一下
Mm. Classing the place up a bit.
翻 译  华晨宇的小宝贝
也就是再也没有长袍了
Which means no more robes.
太俗气了
It's tacky.
他们是有意义的
They're iconic.
我一开始也很怀疑要不要这样
I was skeptical at first, too.
翻 译  马丁
但是  你看
But... look.
我觉得窗帘跟整个房间
I think the curtains really do
翻 译  十二点
真的很搭
tie the room together.
闭嘴  查德  你太过分了
Shut up, Chad. You're out of your element.
你们都应该在
You were all supposed to be
准备召唤魔物的
preparing the pit.
这个啊  我知道我说过
About that, I know that I said
我们完成融合之后就会召唤
we'd raise Malivore after the Merge was done.
但是如果融合成功的话
But if the Merge was successful,
我的姐姐就会已经被我吸收了
I would have absorbed my sister.
特效：小螺号
但是我感觉不到她了
And I can't feel her at all.
不对劲
So something's wrong.
我们猜是霍普搞的鬼
We're guessing it's Hope.
校 对   小狐狸
总是霍普
It's always Hope.
虽然看起来非常紧急  女巫
As urgent as that all seems, witch,
我们接下来做什么由不得你决定
you're not the one who decides what we do next.
特 效   麦 斯
看  这些是我们的玩偶
See, these are my puppets.
我们
We...
接下来要按照我说的做
are gonna do what I say now.
明白了吗
Is that clear
还是我需要让你们点头
or do I need to make you nod?
悉听尊便
Your wish is my command.
用你的僵尸眼看看
Get your zombie eye to find out
丽兹到底怎么了
what really happened to Lizzie.
回去工作
Back to work.
我看上去很平静
I look so peaceful.
甚至像天使
Angelic, even.
难怪你对我有意思
No wonder you had a thing for me.
这不是我之前对你有意思的原因
That's not why I had a thing for you.
为什么要用过去式
And why are you speaking in the past tense?
- 你现在还活着  - 那个花环不能放那里
- You're totally alive. - That wreath can't go there.
那里要放和平鸽
That is where the doves are being released,
就在放完视频之后  还记得吗
which is after the video, remember?
不  丽兹  这不重要好吗
No. Lizzie, this does not matter, okay?
这些都不是真的  这些不过是一场表演
None of this is real. It's just a show.
一个让热门话题杀人乔西相信
A show to convince Homicidal Hot Topic Josie
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
真的是她杀了我的表演
that she actually killed me,
所以最好演得像一点
so it better be a damn good one.
还是有很多事情要做
There's still so much left to do.
如果你要装死
If you're trying to play dead,
自己置办自己的葬礼岂不是暴露真相
managing your own funeral defeats the point.
我早想到了
I'm way ahead of you there.
这就是这个奇怪的大戒指的用途
That is what this freakishly large ring is for.
我是独一无二且特别的
I'm unique and special.
基于某些原因  我很多愁善感
And for some reason, I'm really emo about it.
我去做无谓牺牲的时候  你待在这儿
Wait here while I go sacrifice myself unnecessarily.
我该怎么做
How'd I do?
- 怎么了  - 爸爸
- What's going on here? - Hey, Daddy.
怎么了
What is going on?
我想既然我们把霍普的身体伪装成我的身体
I figured since we're disguising Hope's body as me
在她离开去乔西的意识里探险的时候
while she roots around in Josie's subconscious,
我就可以假装成她
that I could pretend to be her while she's gone.
她真的有这么矮吗
Wow, is she really this short?
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth?
你需要我来监督葬礼
You need me to oversee the funeral.
我们真的支持这样做吗
Are we really gonna roll with this?
会发生的
Like, this is gonna happen...
爸爸
Dad!
一定要真情实感
The emotion has to be real.
而且谁还能比我为自己做的纪念
And who better to put together a touching memorial to me
更感人
than... me?
宝贝  我觉得这个主意真的不错
Uh, sweetie, I think it's a great idea,
但是我想  大家会
but I just... I think people are gonna...
发现的
figure it out.
嗯  他说得对
Yeah, he's right.
狼人绝对不会相信的
The pack's never gonna fall for this.
嗨  都好啊
Ahem. Hello there...
大家伙儿
fellow wolves.
见到你真高兴
So nice to see you again,
派珀  特雷弗  布洛克
Piper, Trevor, Brock.
我们要在葬礼之后
Yo. We're gonna build a human pyramid
玩叠罗汉  你要不要来
after the funeral, if you want to join.
我愿意  也许之后我们可以
I'd love to. And then maybe after we could
出去溜达溜达
run around outside
- 看看天上的月亮  - 好极了
- and stare at the moon for awhile. - Nice.
你真酷  霍普
Yo, you rock, Hope.
你也是  布洛克
Back atcha, Brockmeister.
休息一会吧
The defense rests.
好的  但是不要有鸽子
Fine. But no doves.
行  你听到了
All right, you heard the man.
我们还有事要做
We've got work to do.
萨尔茨曼博士
Dr. Saltzman.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
好
Okay.
你能等等我吗
Hey, would you wait up?
别在我面前一副小红帽
Take your "innocent girl with the basket" act
的样子
someplace else.
我最烦的就是爱好动武的女生
Last thing I need is some trigger-happy skirt
在我旁边施魔法
doing magic near me.
为什么  我施魔法怎么了
Why? What happens if I do magic?
最好别知道
Don't find out!
也别跟着我了
And quit following me.
你不属于这里  宝贝
You don't belong here, toots.
我不喜欢性别歧视的会说话的猪
Sexist talking pigs aren't really my thing.
我可以走  但是在找到我的好朋友乔西之前
I'd love to leave, but I'm not going anywhere
我是不会走的
until I find my friend Josie.
你找她干什么
What do you want with her?
我是来救她的
I came to rescue her.
嗯  好吧  你来晚了
Yeah, well, you're too late for that.
什么意思
What do you mean?
找个树桩坐下
Pull up a stump.
很久之前
Once upon a time,
这个地方以前风景如画
this was a beautiful land.
在乔西特公主的治下宁静祥和
A peaceful kingdom, ruled by Princess Josette.
然后黑暗来袭
And then the Darkness came.
公主也曾与之抗争
The princess tried to fight it,
但是使用她的魔法之后只是让黑暗变得更强了
but using her magic only made the Darkness stronger.
好像跟她是联系起来的  只要她继续抗争
It was tied to her somehow, and if she kept fighting it,
黑暗就会一直蔓延直到笼罩整片土地
the Darkness would grow to cover the entire land.
所以乔西公主就在
So Princess Josie
自己身上施了沉睡咒语
placed a sleeping spell on herself
这样她就永远无法再施魔法了
so that she could never do magic again,
黑暗也就不能继续滋长了
and so that the Darkness could never grow.
如果我们把她叫醒  黑暗就会继续生长
If we wake her up, the Darkness will grow again.
所以  尽管我们都很想她
So... as much as we all miss her,
但是也只能这样
this is how it has to be.
- 命运残酷啊  是吧  - 也许吧
- Destiny's a bitch, huh, doll? - Maybe.
但是我还要试一试
But I still have to try.
换作是她  她也会这么做的
She would do the same for me.
我知道哪里可以找到她了
And I think I know how to find her.
你不会想这样做的
Uh, you don't want to do that.
剩下的面包屑在哪里
Where's the rest of the trail?
是这样的
Well, um, here's the thing.
你肯定不会相信的
You-You're not gonna believe this.
在
The, uh... Whenever, heh,
元素变动之时
the, uh, elements, um...
算了  我坦白被我吃了
Uh, you know what, I ate it.
知道了吗  被我吃了
Okay? I ate it!
哈哈  为什么我会这么做  她问
Ha ha! "Why would I do that?" she asks.
因为我很恶心  因为我没有自制力
Because I'm disgusting, and I have no self-control.
你看到我是什么样子了吗
Do you see the package that I'm working with right now?
好吧  你知道面包屑通向哪里
Okay, you know where this trail goes.
你知道她在哪里
You know where she is.
如果你不告诉我
If you don't tell me
她去了哪里  那我就要开始施法了
where she went, I'm gonna start doing magic.
黑暗也会来的
The Darkness will come.
我就擅长面对黑暗
Facing darkness is kind of my thing.
好吧
Fine.
好
Fine!
你真是蛮横的家伙  你知道吗
You're a bossy little thing, you know that?
在我的世界这算是赞扬
Ah, that's a compliment in my world.
记得提醒我别去那个地方
Remind me not to visit that place.
拉菲  冷静点  好吗
Raf, just calm down, okay?
不管是什么  都不可能有那么严重
Whatever it is, it can't be that bad.
我杀了他  萨尔茨曼博士
I killed him, Dr. Saltzman.
是亡灵法师控制我做的
The Necromancer made me do it.
我们一起来想办法  好吗
We're gonna figure all that out, okay? Just...
没事的
It's okay.
他会活过来的
Look, he's gonna come back.
He'll come back.
这次不会了
Not this time.
乔西  乔西
Josie? Josie?
乔西  醒醒
Josie, wake up.
你也许应该试试亲她
You should try kissing her, maybe.
我知道这虽然是童话
I know this is a fairy tale and all,
但是不经他人同意的亲吻从来不是解决问题的方法
but a nonconsensual kiss is never the answer.
不好意思  能言善道的小姐
Well, excuse me, little Miss Big Words.
你有什么好主意吗
You got a better idea?
新氧
医美
●
新氧视频面诊
医生好不好 当面聊 才知道
医美|皮肤科|齿科|眼科|植发
我有
I do.
醒神明智
Surgere.
- 我们说好了不用魔法  - 我知道你害怕黑暗
- We said no magic. - I know you're scared of the Darkness,
但是这里是乔西的潜意识
but this is Josie's subconscious.
- 没什么能伤害我们  - 哦
- Nothing can really hurt us here. - Oh!
那是什么
What the hell is that?
那就是黑暗  亲爱的
That is the Darkness, sweetheart.
它绝对能伤到我们
And it can definitely hurt us.
小猪
Little pig,
little pig,
你的新朋友在哪
who's your new friend?
我能闻出来
I can smell
这里又有人用魔法了
that magic's being used here again.
去
Saithus.
现在满意了吗  你这蠢丫头
Happy now, you dumb broad?
你差点害我们被吃掉
You nearly got us both eaten...
我跟你说  这是我一辈子最害怕的事
which is a lifelong fear of mine, I'll have you know.
黑暗知道
And now the Darkness knows
你在这使用魔法
your magic-using ass is here.
我的魔法刚刚救了我们的命
Yeah? Well, my magic just saved our asses.
那也是在我把你拉到安全的地方之后
After I pulled you to safety.
谢谢你
Oh, yeah. Thank you
把我拉到一片
so much for pulling me behind
废墟的后面
a single piece of rubble.
你还指望我们能怎么做  我的手是蹄子
What do you want from me? I got hooves for hands.
我希望你不要再对我居高临下地训话
I want you to stop talking down to me
感谢我救了我们的皮肉（猪肉培根）
and be grateful that I just saved our bacon.
你怎么敢这么说
How dare you!
我很抱歉  那只是一种说法
I'm sorry. It's just a figure of speech, all right?
听你站  好吗
Look, truce, okay?
我们都想念乔西
We both miss Josie.
我们可以一起努力把她唤醒
We can work together to wake her up.
如果我们这么做
If we do that,
黑暗只会增长
the Darkness will only grow again.
乔西公主这么做是有原因的
Princess Josie did what she did for a reason.
她作出牺牲
She made her sacrifice
是因为她不知道会有人来帮她
because she didn't know that help was coming.
如果我们不能把她唤醒
So, if we can't wake her up,
我们就得亲自打败黑暗
then we're just gonna have to defeat the Darkness ourselves.
兰登在做什么
What's Landon up to?
我不知道
I don't know.
大概又在什么地方照顾别人
Probably off somewhere being a total beta.
我就喜欢这一点
Which I'm super into.
你要带什么人去参加葬礼吗
You bringing anyone to the funeral?
你们要带同伴去参加葬礼吗
You guys are bringing dates to the funeral?
你们难道
Aren't you in,
不伤心之类的吗
like, mourning or whatever?
为了丽兹吗
Over Lizzie?
我觉得她很受欢迎
I thought she was pretty popular.
因为我们都害怕招惹她
Because we were all scared of crossing her.
用不着担心
It's kind of a relief
她接下来要做什么
to not have to worry about what crazy thing
让人松了一口气
she's going to do next.
另外 又不是说她真就走了
Besides, it's not like she's gone.
既然亡灵法师能够把艾莉莎复活
If The Necromancer brought drama queen Alyssa back,
谁说的准她就不能把丽兹也复活
who's to say he can't bring Lizzie back, too?
很不幸
Unfortunately.
我们需要更多的彩带
We need more ribbon.
有关丽兹的记忆
Memory of Lizzie.
有一次  她设了一道屏障咒
Oh, uh, once, she put up a barrier spell
把我们所有人和滴水石兽困在了一起
and trapped us all in the school with a gargoyle.
不确定她为什么这么做
Um, not really sure why she did that,
但是  相当吓人
but it was... it was pretty scary.
那什么  不是这种的
Yeah, no, uh...
要私密一点的记忆
More like a personal memory.
好吧
Oh. Um... Okay.
有一次她从我身边走过去
Once, she walked by me
无缘无故说了一句休想
and just said, "Hard pass" for no reason.
好吧  停
Um, okay, cut.
我觉得拍得不错
That felt pretty good to me.
你还需要什么吗
Y'all need anything else or... ?
我像
I think...
- 我们会联系你  - 我们再联系你
- We'll call you. - We'll call you.
太好了
Great.
那好
All right.
我们还需要再剪辑一下
Yeah, we're gonna need to edit that last one.
这是追悼会  不是吐槽大会
It's a memorial, not a roast.
这么做毫无意义
Yeah, it's pointless, man.
我们没办法让他们说出有关丽兹的好话
We'll never get them to say anything nice about Lizzie.
这姑娘把全校所有人至少都惹了一遍
Girl has burned everyone in this school at least once.
这不意味我们就要放弃她
Yeah, well, doesn't mean we give up on her.
所有人都认为艾莉莎很刻薄
Everyone thought Alyssa was mean, too.
他们只是不了解真正的她
They just didn't know the real her.
好吧
Okay.
你觉得艾莉莎情况怎么样
You think Alyssa's doing okay?
兄弟  我才不要跟你说这个
Dude, I'm not gonna talk about this.
特别是和你
Especially not with you.
我们已经观察了一整天了
We've been watching the basin all day,
按照要求
as requested.
整个学校  包括混血
The entire school, including the Tribrid,
都在为你妹妹举办追悼会
is planning a memorial for your sister,
而她死了
who is dead.
这我已经知道了
Which we already knew.
我的记忆中有些新事物
There's something new in my mind
我没办法捉摸
that I can't quite reach.
一些不该出现在那的东西
Something that shouldn't be there.
这意味着他们在演戏
That means they're acting.
这意味着他们知道
Which means they know
你放的监视眼
about your little zombie eye.
你被耍了
You've been fooled,
泰德
Ted.
永远不要
Don't ever...
你想让我怎么做
Well, what do you want me to do?
这一定是我父亲的作为
My father must be behind this.
去和他谈谈
Have a chat with him.
我会在我的脑海中
I'll search my mind...
搜寻不寻常的存在
... for the thing that's out of place.
如你所愿
As you wish.
我的天  丽兹
Oh, my God. Lizzie.
- 你还活着  - 别演了  行吗
- You're alive... - Drop it. Okay?
没人在
The coast is clear.
你在做什么
Then what are you doing?
我再也装不下去了
I couldn't pretend for one more second.
没人因为我死了难过
Nobody is upset about me being dead.
他们都恨我
They all hate me.
他们不恨你  丽兹的
They don't hate you, Lizzie's
好朋友霍普
good friend Hope.
我觉得他们
I think
只了解了她的一面
they only just got to know one side of her.
这才是我的悼词要讲的
That's what my eulogy's about.
好主意  如果你想让所有人怀念
Great idea. The perfect eulogy would force everyone to remember
她之前的好这样最合适了
what an amazing person that... she was.
应该由我来说
And I should be the one to do it.
毕竟
After all,
我最了解她
I knew her the best.
我觉得这不是个好主意
I don't, I don't think that's a good idea.
这也是丽兹想要的
It's what Lizzie would've wanted.
好吧
Okay.
这样不对
This is all wrong.
他现在应该复活了
He always comes back by now.
之前从来没有用过这么久
It never takes this long.
别慌  好吗
All right, let's not panic, okay?
语言中说被金箭头所击倒
The prophecy said "felled" by a golden arrow.
击倒可能有多种含义  我们得找到
Now, "felled" could mean anything. We just have to find
原始的科普特单词
the original Coptic word.
你还记得预言中的其它内容吗
Do you remember what else is said in the prophecy?
多面狼
The wolf with many faces.
我杀了他
I killed him.
只要他愿意亡灵法师可以再杀死我
The Necromancer can make me kill again whenever he wants.
听我说  我会把那个怪物从你的脑海中赶出去
Listen to me. I am gonna get that monster out of your head.
不  你得杀了我
No. You got to put me down.
这不行
That is not an option.
听着
Look, look.
我警告过兰登我没办法自持
I warned Landon that I can't control this.
如果你现在不杀了我
Now, if you don't do this now...
也许就来不及了
... then it might be too late.
听着
All right, listen, uh...
我们施一个休眠咒
W-We're gonna get a sleeping spell.
让你处于
All right? And we're gonna put you
静止状态
in a state of suspended animation
等到我们想到解决办法再把你唤醒
until we figure this all out.
我不要再失去学生了
I am not losing another student.
你既然有书了
Then why did you bring that down with you
为什么还要把那个东西拿下来
when you got your book?
那只是个防护措施
That is just a precaution.
我保证所有人的安全
I am trying to keep everyone safe.
我也是啊
So am I!
把剑捡起来
Pick up your sword.
不
No.
快点  捡起来
Do it! Pick it up!
拉夫
Raf...
照做  否则我杀了你
Do it or I will kill you.
我不信
I don't believe you.
捡起来
Pick it up.
你得阻止我
You need to stop me.
兰登的死并非你的错  好吗
You killing Landon is not your fault, okay?
我会想办法救下你们两个人
I'm gonna find a way to save you both.
好吗  兰登的死  不该是由你来负责
All right? You're not responsible for killing Landon.
他可警告过你了  阿拉里克
Well, he did try to warn you, Alaric.
“丽兹”伊丽莎白·萨尔茨曼
我爸呢
Where's my dad?
他随时会到
He'll be here any moment.
关于丽兹的回忆么
A memory of Lizzie?
我非常想念丽兹
I miss Lizzie so bad.
整个学校都会笼罩在悲痛当中
The entire school will never get over it.
丽兹一直都很
Lizzie was always...
很酷
really cool.
很火辣
Really hot.
有很多关于丽兹的回忆
So many memories of Lizzie.
而且我们会记得丽兹这一事实
And the fact that we remember
就说明她并没有堕入黑暗
Lizzie at all means that she didn't go into Malivore.
- 也就是说  有些事  - 行了
- Which, that-that's something... - All right.
遇到了一些技术障碍哈  各位
Technical difficulties, folks.
我们直接跳到下一环节好了
We're just gonna move on with the next part of the service.
谢了
Thank you.
仅以此歌悼念丽兹·萨尔茨曼
This one's for Lizzie Saltzman.
我该如何
* How do I *
向这一切道别
* Say goodbye *
对我们曾经拥有的
* To what we had *
美好时光道别
* The good times *
那些令我们发笑的回忆
* That made us laugh *
总能盖过不好的回忆
* Outweigh the bad *
而我本以为我们可以
* And I thought we'd get *
见证到
* To see... *
* To see *
永恒的友谊
* Forever *
然而永恒却稍纵即逝
* But forever's gone away *
- 行  - 你也知道它已不复存在
- Okay. - * Ooh, you know it's gone *
- 你也知道它已不复存在  - 你也知道它已不复存在
- * You know it's gone * - * You know it's gone away *
嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟  不复存在
* Doo-do-do-do-do-do-do, gone. *
够了哈  多谢啦
Okay, thank you.
感谢你们乱七八糟的表演
Thank you so much for whatever that was.
此时此刻  我想宣读一下
I'm here today to deliver the eulogy
写给伊丽莎白·詹娜·萨尔茨曼的悼词
for Elizabeth Jenna Saltzman.
丽兹不止有一面身份
Lizzie was more than one thing.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
她是个女巫  冒险家  一个完美情人
She was a witch, a daredevil, a lover.
她是个圣人吗
Was she a saint?
这谁能评判
Eh, who's to say?
但是我敢说
But I can say this.
她一定是我们当中最为出色的
She was the absolute best of us.
她有着善良的灵魂
She was a kind soul.
她是那么的善良体贴
She was kind, and nice.
只是偶尔她会感觉疲倦
And sometimes she was just tired
或者一天过得不太舒坦啥的
or having a bad day, or whatever.
你们都自以为明白她的为人  但你们根本不知道
You all think you knew her, but you didn't.
你们都错了
You're all wrong!
奇了怪了  他总是在家的呀
That's strange. He's always home.
有人吗  猎人先生
Hello? Mr. Huntsman.
我给你带了个多管闲事的朋友来啦
I brought a nosy friend.
啊  炖锅还在火上架着  他肯定在附近
Oh, stew's on. He must be nearby.
好耶
Ah. Nice.
亲爱的  如果你以为那把斧头就能阻止黑暗
Sweetie, if you think that's enough to stop the Darkness,
那你就疯了
you are crazy.
或许吧  但我绝不可能不做反抗就任人宰割
Probably, but I'm not going down without a fight.
你说呢
What do you say?
入伙吗
Are you in?
我没有战斗能力啦
I-I would be no use in battle.
我知道  我经常吹牛
I-I know, I bluster a lot.
但我只是害怕了
But, uh, I just get so scared,
我害怕的时候就会胡言乱语
and then I say dumb stuff when I'm scared.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
不过我可以吃点东西
I-I could finish the stew, though.
没准能找到点面包啥的
Maybe find some bread.
在你前去送死之前让你吃顿好的
Uh, make you a nice meal before you go off to die.
行呀  猪头
That'll do, pig.
别得寸进尺  小鬼
Don't press your luck, kiddo.
是陷阱
It's a trap!
小女巫  小女巫
Little witch, little witch,
让我进去吧
let... me... in!
霍普·迈克尔森  你在我脑海里吗
Hope Mikaelson... are you in my head?
什么  怎么回事
Wh-What, what's going on?
这酒吧有新主管了
This pub's under new management.
萨尔茨曼博士
Dr. Saltzman!
他迫使我们与你为敌的
He'll make us fight you.
- 不要轻举妄动  - 他只是想跟你谈谈
- Don't. - He just wants to talk.
确实
It's true.
我有个建议给你
I have an offer for you.
我不会跟你做任何交易
I'm not making any deals with you.
我救你女儿都不行吗
Not even if it saves your daughter?
结果么  咱们俩有同样的目的
Turns out we both want the same thing.
把黑魔法驱逐出她体内
To get that black magic out of her
送她回家
and send her home.
是  但我不需要你的帮助也能做到
Yeah, but I'm doing that without your help.
你是指她脑海中
By which you mean that little
进行的那个自杀任务吗
suicide mission into her mind?
恐怕没用的
Ah, it's going to fail, I'm afraid.
她早就怀疑你们会有所举措了
She already suspects you're up to something.
等她琢磨出你们的伎俩
It's only a matter of time
挫败你们的计划
before she figures out what you're up to
只是时间问题
and puts an end to it.
虽说我不在乎  但是
I wouldn't care either way, but...
我想要那个黑魔法
... I want that black magic
为我掌控
for myself,
然后彻底把那个女孩撵出老子的人生
and that wretched girl out of my life.
善良的乔西还在她体内
The good Josie is still in there,
内心深处某个角落
deep down.
我亲眼所见
I've seen it.
你还得放过他们
You set them free, too.
别玩把戏  无条件放过他们
No strings attached.
有何不可
Why not?
我培养出了这些傀儡
I'll raise these puppets,
之后我会切断我跟他们之间的纽带
then I'll sever my tie with them.
你能救回兰登吗
Can you bring back Landon, too?
当然
Of course.
新氧
医美
●
新氧视频面诊
医生好不好 当面聊 才知道
医美|皮肤科|齿科|眼科|植发
你说你会想办法拯救我们俩
You said you wanted a way to save both of us.
拜托了  你得抓住机会
Come on, you gotta do it.
听这个小子的话
Listen to the lad.
好  但我没有任何理由相信你
Yeah, but there's no way I can trust you.
那就施加一个契约咒吧  谁都不能打破
An unbreakable covenant spell, then.
如果我们没有遵循承诺
If both of us don't hold up our end of the bargain,
咱们俩都没法达到目的
neither of us gets what we want.
你会失去你的傀儡  我会失去我的魔法
You lose your puppets, and I lose me magic.
没有例外可言
No exceptions.
等你决定好了
When you've made up your mind,
你知道如何召唤我
you know how to signal me.
不
No!
小猪
Pig!
怎么回事
What's going on?
我的小猪呢
Where's Pig?
我就是那个小猪
I-I was the pig.
我本以为我易容了
I thought if I disguised myself
黑暗就找不到我
the Darkness would leave me alone.
你就是那只小猪啊
You were the pig?
你知道他跟我说了一些超级自大
You do realize he said some really patronizing
- 还有那些性别歧视的话吗  - 我知道
- and-and sexist things to me. - No, I know.
我只是我不想让你怀疑那是我
I just didn't want you to suspect it was me,
因为我想让你离开这里
because I need you to leave.
好吗  我不想让你受伤
Okay? I don't want you to get hurt.
乔西  我绝不会抛下你一个人的
Josie, I'm not going to leave you behind.
你不明白
No, you don't understand.
我不能再让别人因我而受伤了
I can't have somebody else get hurt because of me.
不会再有了
No one will.
你简直单纯得可爱
I love that you thought it would be that simple.
天呐  快跑
Oh, my God, run!
够了  是时候来场真正的对话了
Okay, time for some real talk.
我有些话要说
I have something to say.
我第一天到这里的时候  是丽兹带领我参观的学校
My first day here, Lizzie was my tour guide.
正如她对你们所有人一样
Just like she was for most of you.
我当时非常畏惧
I was so scared.
而且她也知道
And she knew it, too.
在参观完之后  我说  我讨厌我的名字
At the end of my tour, I mentioned... hating my name,
米尔顿
Milton.
然后她说  那就改掉呗
And she said, "So change it".
没人会知道的  就叫MG怎么样
"No one here knows. How 'bout MG?"
还记得丽兹那个电击手镯吗
Remember that shock bracelet Lizzie had?
或者当她突然迷上了才艺表演的时候
Or when she was suddenly into talent shows
以及神秘瀑布小姐  还有踢足球的事
and-and Miss Mystic Falls, and-and football?
她总是想着从头再来
She was always trying to start over.
确实  有时她的举动很多余  但她心里清楚
And, yeah, she could be extra, but she knew it.
她从未停下改变的脚步
And she never stopped trying to change.
但你们有接纳她的改变吗
But did you all let her?
或者说  你们只是记住了她最糟糕的一面
Or did you hold onto one image of her at her worst?
她是个容易被挑刺的目标
She was an easy target
她没法控制自己大脑中的化学反应
who couldn't control her brain chemistry.
所以比起接纳她  接受她在改变这一事实
So it was easier to think that she was broken than to
认定她是个不堪之人总是要容易得多
root for her and accept that she was changing.
如果你们能抛开成见  反思自己
If you really stop and think,
我相信  你们也会想起丽兹美好的回忆
I'm sure you have a good Lizzie story, too.
现在机会来了
Here's your chance.
重新开始
Start over.
我很喜欢缝纫
I liked to sew a lot.
但是没人陪我一起做
But there was no one else to do it with.
丽兹知道后  她成立了缝纫俱乐部
When Lizzie found out, she started the sewing club.
我们得赶紧跑
We have to keep moving.
无所谓了  反正我们也逃不掉了
It doesn't matter, we're never gonna get away from her.
乔  你困在这
Jo, while you've been trapped in here,
她可是在外面猖狂得狠呀
she's been rampaging in the real world.
她甚至试图与丽兹融合
Okay, she even tried to Merge with Lizzie.
天呐  她还好吗
Oh, my God, is she okay?
暂时还好  所以我们得阻止她
For now. But that's why we have to stop her.
- 她比我强大多了  - 乔
- She's more powerful than I am. - Jo...
她就是你
... she is you.
你身体的一部分
Or some part of you.
你可以想法控制她的
You can control her somehow.
虽然我不知道怎么做
I don't know how, but...
兰登会讲些心理学的理论
Landon would have some theory about the psychology,
讲她体现的是你人格中的哪些部分
and what part of your personality she represents.
他会的  是吗
He would, wouldn't he?
你这的
Pretty messed-up subconscious
潜意识很混乱
you got here, by the way.
这很令人惊讶吗
Are we surprised?
我妈妈经常睡前
My mom used to read us fairy tales
给我们读童话故事
for bedtime stories.
童话故事很让人安心
They were so calming.
有好人有坏人
There was good guys and bad guys.
我们要遵守的规则也很明确
Very clear rules that you had to follow.
都能说通
It all made sense.
不像我的生活
Unlike my life.
那些童话故事烂透了
Well, this fairy tale sucks.
我觉得说的很准啊  我要么是强大的贱人
It's accurate. I'm either the powerful, petty bitch
要么是软弱的好人
or the good, weak victim.
那是你自己编造的故事
That's the story that you're telling yourself.
你潜意识里编出了个童话故事
I mean, your subconscious made a fairy tale
好人软弱  坏人强大
that the good you is weak and the powerful you is evil.
你完全可以改写你的故事
Tell yourself a different story.
无聊
Boring.
开打吧
Let's fight.
第一次
That's strike one.
统统退散
Icaeus...
谢谢你给我输送魔法
Ah, thanks for the extra magic.
第二次
That's strike two.
乔西  你能打过她的
Josie, you can fight her.
三振出局
Hmm, that's strike three.
乔西  重写故事
Josie! Change the story.
拜托不要
Please.
我恨你
I hate you.
你真是手无缚鸡之力
You're so weak
不堪一击
and vulnerable.
这么文静的女孩
The kind of girl who's so quiet
活在丽兹的阴影下
that her father and mother forget about her
爸爸妈妈都忽略她
in the chaos of Lizzie.
那种佩内洛普不会再追求的那种女孩
The kind of girl Penelope won't fight for anymore.
那种兰登在一次演讲中分手的女孩
The kind of girl Landon breaks up with in one speech.
那种注定在融合中输掉的女孩
The kind of girl who's destined to lose the Merge.
你需要我
You needed me.
没有了我
Because without me,
你没法生存的
you would have never survived.
强大的人就长姐这样
This is what being strong looks like.
这只是你的版本
That's the story that you're telling yourself.
好人软弱  坏人强大
That the good you is weak, and the powerful you is evil.
我害怕变强
I was afraid of being strong.
我以为变强意味着会伤害丽兹
I thought being strong meant hurting Lizzie.
乔西  拜托
Oh! Josie, please!
那就是变得强大的样子
Here's what being strong looks like.
像凯那样  我告诉自己
Or being like Kai. I told myself
强大就会变成魔鬼
that being powerful meant being evil.
但是其实不会
But it doesn't.
霍普是强大的
Hope is strong.
而且她没有作恶
And she's good.
你编造了一个故事
You made a story...
我的故事里
I made a story...
自己是软弱无力的
where I was powerless.
但事实并非如此
But that's not true.
因为我可以改写自己的故事
Because I can change this story.
够了
Enough.
我不怕你了
I'm not afraid of you anymore.
现在斧头在我手中
Because I'm holding the Axe.
禁身锁魂
Finidus...
我把你囚禁在这个小木屋
I just bound you to this cabin.
我永远都别想出去
You're trapped here forever.
你困不住我的
I'm not trapped.
现在我们不在小木屋了
Because we're not in the cabin anymore.
你要是用魔法对付我的话
And... if you use your magic against me,
你自己也会遭到反噬
it hurts you, too.
但最重要的是
But most importantly...
你没有盔甲了
... you're not wearing armor anymore.
都结束了
It's over.
不会结束的
It'll never be over.
只要你身体里还有黑魔法
As long as you have black magic in you.
我就能想办法回来
I will always find a way back.
等着瞧吧
We'll see.
咒语
Magia tollox De terras...
魔力退散
释放
Solvo.
- 嘿我自己可以的  - 嘿  帅哥们
- Hey, I got this myself. - Hey, studs.
你自己可以吗
Uh... You got it yourself?
- 艾莉莎  你  - 回来了
- Alyssa. Um, are you... ? - Back?
挺好的  不是个傀儡了
Fine? Not a zombie?
都是小事
Don't make it a big thing.
或许等会  我们
Um, maybe later, we can, uh...
好吧
Okay.
嗯你
Yeah. You...
你想说说吗
You want to talk about this?
不是朋友我  她  我挺好的
No, man, she be... I'm good.
她不该那么粗鲁的
She didn't have to be rude.
- 伤我心了  - 真的吗  我们也是人啊
- Is really the thing. - Right? We're people, too.
- 人  - 我是说  我们也有感情的
- People. - I mean, I have feelings.
谢谢你没有放弃我
Thank you for not giving up on me.
尽管我不值得你这么做
Even though I didn't deserve it.
做爸爸快乐的就是
You know, one of the many joys of being your father
看着你慢慢
is getting to see you slowly
找到自己应该得到什么
figure out how much you deserve.
某天你会意识到你值得
And one day, you'll realize that what you deserve
有人会你坚守
is to never be given up on.
等到全能的亡灵巫师回来
Tell me that when the all-powerful Necromancer
你就不这么想了
comes back.
时机到了自然有办法对付他
We'll deal with him when the time comes.
我不想再失去我的学生了
I'm not willing to lose another student.
束法移魔
Oribos turai filio...
我曾看到你的生母施过这样的咒语
I saw your biological mother do a spell like that once.
你刚刚是
Did you just... ?
我只是把我的虹吸能量封锁进这个硬币里了
I just put my siphon power into this coin.
放段时间
Just... just for a while.
等我准备好使用它了再说
Till I'm ready to use it.
仔细想想  悼词只是
When you think about it, a eulogy is just a story
讲述我们失去了某个人的故事
that we tell ourselves about someone that we've lost.
因为我的朋友MG永生不死
Since my friend MG is immortal,
他肯定用不上悼词
he may never get a eulogy.
但我相信
But I am now convinced
每个人都应该听到自己的悼词
that everyone should hear their own eulogy.
所以这就是
So here goes.
MG的故事
The story of MG.
他的父亲是一名牧师
He was the son of a preacher
他是名秘密政府探员
and a shady government operative.
他只保留美好  不计较坏事
He kept what was good from each and let go of the bad.
他也有邪恶的一面
He had his own demons,
但尽管邪恶把他逼近黑暗角落
but even when they chased him into the dark,
他也从未停留
he never stayed there.
相反地
Instead,
他像烟火般绚烂
he danced like a sparkler
他的笑容好比太阳
and smiled like the sun.
他每天书写一个全新的故事
He wrote a new story every day,
提醒我时刻找到光明
and reminded me to always find the light.
我就能想到这么多了
That's as far as I got.
我不知道故事从哪里开始
I don't know where the story goes from there.
只是还没写出来  我想
Just hasn't been written yet, I guess.
谢谢你今天听我说这些
Thank you for... putting up with me today.
我想经过乔西那件事之后
I guess after all the stuff that happened with Josie,
我就是很需要
I just... really needed to feel...
尽量不自己呆着
less alone.
我明白
I know.
我或许应该跟大家说说
I should probably go and explain
为什么我没死
to everyone why I'm not really dead.
丽兹
Lizzie?
你还活着
You're alive?
嗨
Hi.
他还没有
He hasn't, uh... ?
我不明白
I don't get it.
亡灵巫师放了我和艾丽莎
The Necromancer freed me and Alyssa,
但是兰登他  他还没醒来
but Landon, he... he won't wake up.
是的  我们说好的
Yeah, but we had a deal.
他履行了一部分约定
He made good on part of it.
我又有心跳了  我活过来了
My heartbeat's back. I'm alive.
脑子里不再有
It doesn't feel like I have that little voice
那些声音了
in my head anymore.
我自由了
I'm free.
兰登现在也该回来了
Landon should be back by now.
是的
Yeah.
这不是我们唯一的问题
That's not our only problem.
我不明白  她到底怎么了
I don't understand. What's wrong with her?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
但她还没醒
But she won't wake up.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）